[
  {
    "id": "001C",
    "question_text": "What is the probability of rain in Recife(pink) below 100 mm?",
    "op": [
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Recife"
    ],
    "answer": "47",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "002C",
    "question_text": "What is the probability of rain in Jaboatão dos Guararapes(pink) above 100 mm?",
    "op": [
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Jaboatão dos Guararapes"
    ],
    "answer": "56",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "003C",
    "question_text": "What is the probability of rain in São Lourenço da Mata(pink) between 50 and 150 mm?",
    "op": [
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "São Lourenço da Mata"
    ],
    "answer": "33",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "004C",
    "question_text": "Between Ipojuca (pink) and Cabo de Santo Agostinho(blue), which of the two cities is most likely to rain bellow 100 mm?",
    "op": [
      "Ipojuca",
      "Cabo de Santo Agostinho"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Ipojuca",
      "Cabo de Santo Agostinho"
    ],
    "answer": "Ipojuca",
    "distance": "Short",
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "005C",
    "question_text": "What is the probability of rain in Ipojuca(pink) be less than in Cabo de Santo Agostinho(blue)?",
    "op": [
      "Ipojuca",
      "Cabo de Santo Agostinho"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Ipojuca",
      "Cabo de Santo Agostinho"
    ],
    "answer": "67",
    "distance": "Short",
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "006C",
    "question_text": "What is the probability of rain in Recife(pink) be less than in Santa Cruz(blue)?",
    "op": [
      "Recife",
      "Santa Cruz"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Recife",
      "Santa Cruz"
    ],
    "answer": "14",
    "distance": "Long",
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "007C",
    "question_text": "What is the probability of rain in Jataúba(pink) be less than in Petrolândia(blue)?",
    "op": [
      "Jataúba",
      "Petrolândia"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Jataúba",
      "Petrolândia"
    ],
    "answer": "64",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": "Low",
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "008C",
    "question_text": "What is the probability of rain in Tacaratú(pink) be less than in Araripina(blue)?",
    "op": [
      "Tacaratu",
      "Araripina"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Tacaratu",
      "Araripina"
    ],
    "answer": "47",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": "High",
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "009C",
    "question_text": "What is the probability of rain in Saloá(pink) be less than in Pombos(blue)?",
    "op": [
      "Saloá",
      "Pombos"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Saloá",
      "Pombos"
    ],
    "answer": "56",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": "Small"
  },
  {
    "id": "010C",
    "question_text": "What is the probability of rain in Sertânia(pink) be less than in Parnamirim(blue)?",
    "op": [
      "Sertânia",
      "Parnamirim"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Sertânia",
      "Parnamirim"
    ],
    "answer": "53",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": "Large"
  },
  {
    "id": "011C",
    "question_text": "Select in the list the name of the city that is most likely to rain below 100 mm?",
    "op": [
      "Abreu e Lima", "Afogados da Ingazeira", "Afrânio", "Agrestina", "Água Preta", "Águas Belas", "Alagoinha", "Aliança", "Altinho", "Amaraji", "Angelim", "Araçoiaba", "Araripina", "Arcoverde", "Barra de Guabiraba", "Barreiros", "Belém de Maria", "Belém de São Francisco", "Belo Jardim", "Betânia", "Bezerros", "Bodocó", "Bom Conselho", "Bom Jardim", "Bonito", "Brejão", "Brejinho", "Brejo da Madre de Deus", "Buenos Aires", "Buíque", "Cabo de Santo Agostinho", "Cabrobó", "Cachoeirinha", "Caetés", "Calçado", "Calumbi", "Camaragibe", "Camocim de São Félix", "Camutanga", "Canhotinho", "Capoeiras", "Carnaíba", "Carnaubeira da Penha", "Carpina", "Caruaru", "Casinhas", "Catende", "Cedro", "Chã de Alegria", "Chã Grande", "Condado", "Correntes", "Cortês", "Cumaru", "Cupira", "Custódia", "Dormentes", "Escada", "Exu", "Feira Nova", "Ferreiros", "Flores", "Floresta", "Frei Miguelinho", "Gameleira", "Garanhuns", "Glória do Goitá", "Goiana", "Granito", "Gravatá", "Iati", "Ibimirim", "Ibirajuba", "Igarassu", "Iguaraci", "Inajá", "Ingazeira", "Ipojuca", "Ipubi", "Itacuruba", "Itaíba", "Ilha de Itamaracá", "Itambé", "Itapetim", "Itapissuma", "Itaquitinga", "Jaboatão dos Guararapes", "Jaqueira", "Jataúba", "Jatobá", "João Alfredo", "Joaquim Nabuco", "Jucati", "Jupi", "Jurema", "Lagoa do Carro", "Lagoa do Itaenga", "Lagoa do Ouro", "Lagoa dos Gatos", "Lagoa Grande",
      "Lajedo", "Limoeiro", "Macaparana", "Machados", "Manari", "Maraial", "Mirandiba", "Moreno", "Nazaré da Mata", "Olinda", "Orobó", "Orocó", "Ouricuri", "Palmares", "Palmeirina", "Panelas", "Paranatama", "Parnamirim", "Passira", "Paudalho", "Paulista", "Pedra", "Pesqueira", "Petrolândia", "Petrolina", "Poção", "Pombos", "Primavera", "Quipapá", "Quixaba", "Recife", "Riacho das Almas", "Ribeirão", "Rio Formoso", "Sairé", "Salgadinho", "Salgueiro", "Saloá", "Sanharó", "Santa Cruz", "Santa Cruz da Baixa Verde", "Santa Cruz do Capibaribe", "Santa Filomena", "Santa Maria da Boa Vista", "Santa Maria do Cambucá", "Santa Terezinha", "São Benedito do Sul", "São Bento do Una", "São Caetano", "São João", "São Joaquim do Monte", "São José da Coroa Grande", "São José do Belmonte", "São José do Egito", "São Lourenço da Mata", "São Vicente Ferrer", "Serra Talhada", "Serrita", "Sertânia", "Sirinhaém", "Moreilândia", "Solidão", "Surubim", "Tabira", "Tacaimbó", "Tacaratu", "Tamandaré", "Taquaritinga do Norte", "Terezinha", "Terra Nova", "Timbaúba", "Toritama", "Tracunhaém", "Trindade", "Triunfo", "Tupanatinga", "Tuparetama", "Venturosa", "Verdejante", "Vertente do Lério", "Vertentes", "Vicência", "Vitória de Santo Antão", "Xexéu"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "Jatobá",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "012C",
    "question_text": "Select in the list the name of the city that is least likely to rain below 100 mm?",
    "op": [
      "Abreu e Lima", "Afogados da Ingazeira", "Afrânio", "Agrestina", "Água Preta", "Águas Belas", "Alagoinha", "Aliança", "Altinho", "Amaraji", "Angelim", "Araçoiaba", "Araripina", "Arcoverde", "Barra de Guabiraba", "Barreiros", "Belém de Maria", "Belém de São Francisco", "Belo Jardim", "Betânia", "Bezerros", "Bodocó", "Bom Conselho", "Bom Jardim", "Bonito", "Brejão", "Brejinho", "Brejo da Madre de Deus", "Buenos Aires", "Buíque", "Cabo de Santo Agostinho", "Cabrobó", "Cachoeirinha", "Caetés", "Calçado", "Calumbi", "Camaragibe", "Camocim de São Félix", "Camutanga", "Canhotinho", "Capoeiras", "Carnaíba", "Carnaubeira da Penha", "Carpina", "Caruaru", "Casinhas", "Catende", "Cedro", "Chã de Alegria", "Chã Grande", "Condado", "Correntes", "Cortês", "Cumaru", "Cupira", "Custódia", "Dormentes", "Escada", "Exu", "Feira Nova", "Ferreiros", "Flores", "Floresta", "Frei Miguelinho", "Gameleira", "Garanhuns", "Glória do Goitá", "Goiana", "Granito", "Gravatá", "Iati", "Ibimirim", "Ibirajuba", "Igarassu", "Iguaraci", "Inajá", "Ingazeira", "Ipojuca", "Ipubi", "Itacuruba", "Itaíba", "Ilha de Itamaracá", "Itambé", "Itapetim", "Itapissuma", "Itaquitinga", "Jaboatão dos Guararapes", "Jaqueira", "Jataúba", "Jatobá", "João Alfredo", "Joaquim Nabuco", "Jucati", "Jupi", "Jurema", "Lagoa do Carro", "Lagoa do Itaenga", "Lagoa do Ouro", "Lagoa dos Gatos", "Lagoa Grande",
      "Lajedo", "Limoeiro", "Macaparana", "Machados", "Manari", "Maraial", "Mirandiba", "Moreno", "Nazaré da Mata", "Olinda", "Orobó", "Orocó", "Ouricuri", "Palmares", "Palmeirina", "Panelas", "Paranatama", "Parnamirim", "Passira", "Paudalho", "Paulista", "Pedra", "Pesqueira", "Petrolândia", "Petrolina", "Poção", "Pombos", "Primavera", "Quipapá", "Quixaba", "Recife", "Riacho das Almas", "Ribeirão", "Rio Formoso", "Sairé", "Salgadinho", "Salgueiro", "Saloá", "Sanharó", "Santa Cruz", "Santa Cruz da Baixa Verde", "Santa Cruz do Capibaribe", "Santa Filomena", "Santa Maria da Boa Vista", "Santa Maria do Cambucá", "Santa Terezinha", "São Benedito do Sul", "São Bento do Una", "São Caetano", "São João", "São Joaquim do Monte", "São José da Coroa Grande", "São José do Belmonte", "São José do Egito", "São Lourenço da Mata", "São Vicente Ferrer", "Serra Talhada", "Serrita", "Sertânia", "Sirinhaém", "Moreilândia", "Solidão", "Surubim", "Tabira", "Tacaimbó", "Tacaratu", "Tamandaré", "Taquaritinga do Norte", "Terezinha", "Terra Nova", "Timbaúba", "Toritama", "Tracunhaém", "Trindade", "Triunfo", "Tupanatinga", "Tuparetama", "Venturosa", "Verdejante", "Vertente do Lério", "Vertentes", "Vicência", "Vitória de Santo Antão", "Xexéu"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "Amaraji",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "013C",
    "question_text": "What is the average rainfall in the city of Caruaru(pink)?",
    "op": [
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Caruaru"
    ],
    "answer": "50",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
    {
    "id": "014T",
    "question_text": "What is the probability that the number of taxi races in the West Chelsea/Hudson Yards(pink) be less than 18.000?",
    "op": [
    ],
    "highlights": [
      246
    ],
    "answer": "75",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "015T",
    "question_text": "What is the probability that the number of taxi races in the West Chelsea/Hudson Yards(pink) above 20.000?",
    "op": [
    ],
    "highlights": [
      246
    ],
    "answer": "8",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "016T",
    "question_text": "What is the probability that the number of taxi races in the Times Sq/Theater District(pink) be between 18.000 and 35.000?",
    "op": [
    ],
    "highlights": [
      230
    ],
    "answer": "33",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
    {
    "id": "017T",
    "question_text": "Between Midtown South(pink) and Murray Hill(blue), which of the two areas is most likely to have number of taxi races below 27.000?",
    "op": [
      "Midtown South",
      "Murray Hill"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      164,
      170
    ],
    "answer": "Midtown South",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "018T",
    "question_text": "What is the probability that the number of cab rides in Clinton East(pink) be less than Times Sq/Theatre District(blue)?",
    "op": [
      "Clinton East",
      "Times Sq/Theatre District"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      48,
      230
    ],
    "answer": "42",
    "distance": "Short",
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "019T",
    "question_text": "What is the probability that the number of taxi races in West Village(pink) be less than Midtown North(blue)?",
    "op": [
      "West Village",
      "Midtown North"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      249,
      163
    ],
    "answer": "25",
    "distance": "Long",
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "020T",
    "question_text": "What is the probability that the number of taxi races in Lenox Hill West(pink) be less than Gramercy(blue)?",
    "op": [
      "Lenox Hill West",
      "Gramercy"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      141,
      107
    ],
    "answer": "83",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": "Low",
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "021T",
    "question_text": "What is the probability that the number of taxi races in West Village(pink) be less than Murray Hill(blue)?",
    "op": [
      "West Village",
      "Murray Hill"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      249,
      170
    ],
    "answer": "92",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": "High",
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "022T",
    "question_text": "What is the probability that the number of taxi races in Central Park(pink) be less than Greenwich Village North(blue)?",
    "op": [
      "Central Park",
      "Greenwich Village North"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      43,
      113
    ],
    "answer": "75",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": "Small"
  },
  {
    "id": "023T",
    "question_text": "What is the probability that the number of taxi races in Union Sq(pink) be less than Midtown Center(blue)?",
    "op": [
      "Union Sq",
      "Midtown Center"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      234,
      161
    ],
    "answer": "42",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": "Large"
  },
  {
    "id": "024T",
    "question_text": "Select in the list the name of the area most likely to have a taxi race number above 34.000?",
    "op": [
      "Central Park", "Clinton East", "Clinton West", "East Chelsea", "East Village", "Flatiron", "Garment District", "Gramercy", "Greenwich Village North", "Kips Bay", "Lenox Hill East", "Lenox Hill West", "Lincoln Square East", "Meatpacking/West Village West", "Midtown Center", "Midtown East", "Midtown North", "Midtown South", "Murray Hill", "Penn Station/Madison Sq West", "Roosevelt Island", "Stuy Town/Peter Cooper Village", "Sutton Place/Turtle Bay North", "Times Sq/Theatre District", "UN/Turtle Bay South", "Union Sq", "Upper East Side South", "West Chelsea/Hudson Yards", "West Village"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "Penn Station/Madison Sq West",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "025T",
    "question_text": "Select in the list the name of the area that is least likely to have a taxi race number above 3.500?",
    "op": [
      "Central Park", "Clinton East", "Clinton West", "East Chelsea", "East Village", "Flatiron", "Garment District", "Gramercy", "Greenwich Village North", "Kips Bay", "Lenox Hill East", "Lenox Hill West", "Lincoln Square East", "Meatpacking/West Village West", "Midtown Center", "Midtown East", "Midtown North", "Midtown South", "Murray Hill", "Penn Station/Madison Sq West", "Roosevelt Island", "Stuy Town/Peter Cooper Village", "Sutton Place/Turtle Bay North", "Times Sq/Theatre District", "UN/Turtle Bay South", "Union Sq", "Upper East Side South", "West Chelsea/Hudson Yards", "West Village"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "Roosevelt Island",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "026T",
    "question_text": "Estimate what is the average number of taxi races in the Gramercy(pink) area?",
    "op": [
    ],
    "highlights": [
      107
    ],
    "answer": "25000",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  }
]